export const data = [
  {
    id: "0",
    question: "Crabs are decapods. How many legs does this mean they have??",
    answer: "10",
    options: ["6", "8", "10", "Depends"],
    difficulty: "1",
  },
  {
    id: "1",
    question: "What do crabs eat?",
    options: ["Seaweed", "Other crabs", "Worms", "Pretty much anything"],
    answer: "Pretty much anything",
    difficulty: "2",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    question: "Crabs live on land as well as in the sea. True or false?",
    options: [
      "Land crabs? Never heard anything so stupid in my life!",
      "Land crabs? You betcha",
    ],
    answer: "Land crabs? Never heard anything so stupid in my life!",
    difficulty: "2",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    question:
      "Like insects, crab shells are made of a hard material called chitin. Can you guess which of these things is also made out of chitin?",
    options: ["Trees", "Seaweed", "Mushrooms", "Sand"],
    answer: "Seaweed",
    difficulty: "4",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    question:
      "What crab-related fluid is very expensive? Honestly - it's about Â£10,000 a litre!",
    options: [
      "Fiddler crab tears",
      "Snow crab wee",
      "Blue crab sweat",
      "Horseshoe crab blood",
    ],
    answer: "Horseshoe crab blood",
    difficulty: "4",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    question: "What's the fancy name for a crab's shell?",
    options: ["Armour", "Plating", "Ectoskeleton", "Exoskeleton"],
    answer: "Ectoskeleton",
    difficulty: "3",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    question: "A lobster is just a type of weird looking crab. True or false?",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "False",
    difficulty: "2",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    question: "If you're at the beach and see a crab, what should you do?",
    options: [
      "Take a look - but leave it alone.",
      "Run away!",
      "Feed it chips",
      "Introduce it to your family",
    ],
    answer: "Take a look - but leave it alone.",
    difficulty: "1",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    question: "Crabs belong to a group of animals known as the Crustaceans.",
    options: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "True",
    difficulty: "2",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    question:
      "The scientific name for the common (or green) shore crab is what?",
    options: [
      "Cancer pagurus",
      "Necora puber",
      "Pagurus bernhardus",
      "Carcinus maenas",
    ],
    answer: "Carcinus maenas",
    difficulty: "4",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    question: "Out of 1-2 million eggs, how many will survive to maturity?",
    options: ["1-2", "10-20", "100-200", "1000-2000"],
    answer: "1-2",
    difficulty: "3",
  },
];
